Here's the top answer.
It's in the Hirokawa.
He's leaving change.
More and more daviews.
This one is still in the middle.
I love that look too much.
He's still hiding it.
He's still hiding the change.
I know, right?
I'm updating this page with a shared, perpetual obsession.
You, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you.
Rasta's Official Video Program
Lalatube
Lori Lori Lori
Already gone 20
I can't breathe when you love me
I'm crazy about you, I can't take it anymore
Show me more
Not at all!
Updating.
A little bit of time
Doki-Doki Doki Doki Meki-Meki-Ya Marecho
I can dance
I'll let you lead me
It's not fair, isn't it, that smile
I'm going to love you even more
Still hiding something
You're still leaving the change
Kuneyo!
I'm crazy about her.
I love that expression too much
She's still hiding something.
There's still a change left.
I know, right?
I'm updating this in a shared, perpetual obsession.
I want to know you, you, you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you, and you
I love you so much I can't breathe.
Who was your hair stylist today?
I'm not at MVB today.
I'm always with Asha and MVB and all kinds of people.
I'd like to say something different.
Okay, then.
Success should happen many times!
LOL.
I'm still hiding something.
I still have a change left.
Touching Radian.
This is still absurd.
That look is too much.
He's still hiding something.
He's still got the change.
Right?
I'm in the middle of a shared, perpetual obsession update.
I want to get to know you, and you, and you, and you, and everything.
Yay.
One last one.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
I got the part.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work
Thanks for your hard work!
rpm
Thank you very much
thank you
you mentioned
start Simple
S sencill
C
так
How's it going?
Oh
like
Night
For the first time
dream
C
f
t
I am Pearl.
How did it go? Today's shoot?
Who are you talking to?
The manager.
It was good.
You were adorable.
How cute was your personal shoot, Miri?
Today was your first time at Aisha's with Takamine twintails.
I see.
It was idol-like.
It's a nostalgic Aisha look.
I think it turned out well.
If it suits you, I'm sure we'll do it again next time.
Please tell me you guys are doing it...
Please tell me.
Thank you very much.
Here is one song for the beach ball.
In this face, I'm smiling.
It looks like fun.
I think.
I will never fall.
We are done.
Thank you very much.
We're done.
It's over.
I feel like I've eaten a complete meal this time.
It feels like summer.
It's a good feeling.
One week later, we are going to shoot a music video.
The choreography is not done yet.
Good luck and then
me
Hm...
nasya
We have a lot of photos lined up at the site.
We are running a little low on stock.
We also have new items!
This is Nickless.
Nickless is one of our best sellers.
Please buy it!
It's a cute item.
We'll see you online or something.
Please hook me up!
Hello everyone!
Today is the FIMS pop-up!
Friday is the 14th and 56th!
This is the 3rd day!
Saturday and Sunday, one day
Thank you to everyone who participated in the Shark Squadron!
Thank you so much!
When I was taking pictures, there were so many people all wearing the same clothes.
They were all looking at me. Thank you so much.
I hope you all have a great summer and beyond with these really nice clothes.
Personally, I think the bat was shown very well, especially by the younger members.
I hope you will continue to support the younger members and me as well.
Please take good care of them.
It was a pleasure to pop up in such a nice place.
It was a pleasure to do the pop-up!
I hope you will make a reservation.
Thank you very much.
The cup up is over. Thank you very much.
I am so grateful to have had the opportunity to do a pop-up in such a nice place for three days.
I'm glad to see that the shirts are toast here too.
Good luck to you.
Thanks again, Isshi.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
I just changed, and I was hit with a one-ship.
I'm a little embarrassed to be taking a video.
But I think it's really precious to be able to have an exhibition like this in such a great big city like Lahore Harajuku.
I think it's really precious to be able to hold an exhibition like this in such a great metropolis like Lahore Harajuku.
I think it's really precious to be able to exhibit clothes and hats that I designed from scratch
I was really happy and it warmed my heart to see the clothes and hats that I designed from scratch
I was really happy and it warmed my heart.
I'm sure that HIM-TETA will continue again.
Please look forward to the fall and winter season!
Thank you very much!
All right, all right, all right.
Mechanical announcement.
This time HIM-TETA's HOT UP
HIM-TETA's HOT UP was held at Lavoir, a place I visit often.
I'm so thankful that we were able to do this.
I was so thankful to be able to have a very spacious and
We had a very spacious and stylish store.
T-shirts were also available this time.
I think it's pretty good.
Pretty cool!
It's cool.
This time
Necklace
I use silver a lot, so I made it out of silver, and the other members' items are cute too,
I am really happy that the drama of the burst was able to be made into a series.
I was really happy that so many people came to the event.
Thank you so much, I'm really happy that so many people came.
Thanks for coming.
How was it? Today's shooting.
Who are you talking to?
The manager.
It was good.